const STORE = [
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is NOT a leave-no-trace principle?',
        answers: ['Respect wildlife', 'Pack out all trash', 'Bushwack when needed - some crags are difficult to find.', 
        'Bring food, water, and essential climbing gear'],
        correctAnswer: 'Bushwack when needed - some crags are difficult to find.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What does the climbing etiquitte at the Red River Gorge say about cleaning?',
        answers: ['Always lower.', 'Always rapel.', 'Lower or rapel, whichever you want.', 'There is no etiquette surrounding cleaning techniques.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Always lower.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is poor etiquette?',
        answers: ['Ticking all of the essential holds on the route and leaving them up to help future climbers send.', 
        'Hanging hammocks out of the way of main hiking trails and belay spots.', 'Picking up trash, even if its not yours.',
    'Letting other people work in if you have a large group of people on a route.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Ticking all of the essential holds on the route and leaving them up to help future climbers send.'
    },
    {
        question: 'What should you do if you arrive at a crag and it\'s overly crowded?',
        answers: ['Climb there anyways.', 'Go to a different crag.', 'Heckle other climbers into leaving.',
    'None of the above.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Go to a different crag.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is NOT a reason why we respect local climbing ethics?',
        answers: ['Climbing as a sport is exploding. This means more people at the crag, which means it is more important than ever before to protect the land we have.',
    'We are not entitled to the areas we rock climb at. We can lose these privilages.', 'Good question... I don\'t know',
'A lot of rules are in place to protect your safety.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Good question... I don\'t know'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following is NOT true about bolting in the Red River Gorge?',
        answers: ['Due to the rock type and humidity, zinc plated hardware is corroding.',
    'Stainless steel glue-ins are being used to replace bolts across the U.S. and are a more sustainable option.',
'The Red River Gorge Fixed Gear Initiative is working to replace corroded bolts and has already replaced over 1,000 bolts with donations.',
'Stainless steel glue-ins are the best option because of how cheap they are.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Stainless steel glue-ins are the best option because of how cheap they are.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following statements about group sizing is NOT true?',
        answers: ['Let other people work into climbs you are on.', 'Spread your group apart - not everyone should be in line for the same climb. Split up in pairs.',
    'The philosophy on group sizing is: "The more, the merrier!"', 'Large groups can lead to a noisy and disruptive crag.'],
        correctAnswer: 'The philosophy on group sizing is: "The more, the merrier!"'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following statements about trails is TRUE?',
        answers: ['Always walk around mud - walking through just makes the problem worse.', 'Walk through the mud - walking around could lead to a wider trail.',
    'It doesn\'t matter if you walk through the mud or around the mud.', 'None of the above.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Walk through the mud - walking around could lead to a wider trail.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following about human waste at the crag is FALSE?',
        answers: ['As long as you are off the main walking trail, you are fine.', 'Pee at least 200 feet away from water sources.',
    'Dig a hole with a shovel and burry the TP along with the waste or pack out all waste if possible.',
'If there is an established bathroom, be sure to go before you climb or hike in.'],
        correctAnswer: 'As long as you are off the main walking trail, you are fine.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following statements is FALSE?',
        answers: ['Carpool to save on fuel and parking spaces.', 'Keep the group size small.', 
        'Take the most efficient route to the crag. Cut switchbacks.', 'Stay away from sensitive or eroded areas.'],
        correctAnswer: 'Take the most efficient route to the crag. Cut switchbacks.'
    },
]